<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tony&#39;s Cybersecurity Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tony&#39;s Cybersecurity Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Anthony Morell</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-29513: Stored XSS in NodeBB Admin API token generator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cve-2025-29513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cve-2025-29513/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CVE-2025-29513 is a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability in the Admin API token generator functionality of NodeBB version 4.0.4 and below. This flaw allows an attacker with administrative access to inject arbitrary JavaScript through crafted input in the User ID (uid) field when generating new API tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Although the frontend input form enforces numeric validation, an attacker can bypass these restrictions by using tools like cURL or a web proxy to submit values such as -0 or malformed numeric strings (e.g., -0000.00). These inputs are not properly validated server-side and are reflected in the rendered HTML of the admin panel, leading to persistent script injection.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-29512: Stored XSS in the blacklist IP functionality</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cve-2025-29512/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 02:01:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cve-2025-29512/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CVE-2025-29512 is a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability affecting NodeBB version 4.0.4 and below. The issue resides in the IP blacklist administration panel &lt;code&gt;/ip-blacklist&lt;/code&gt;, where input provided to the &amp;ldquo;rules&amp;rdquo; &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;textarea&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; is improperly sanitized. When a moderator inputs malicious HTML or JavaScript, the payload is stored and executed upon subsequent visits to the page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This vulnerability allows moderators to execute arbitrary JavaScript in the context of other privileged users, leading to potential session hijacking, defacement, or unauthorized administrative actions. Since the injected script persists across sessions and there is no built-in mechanism to sanitize or remove the stored payload from the UI, exploitation can lead to persistent denial of access to the page or further abuse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2024-57041: Stored XSS in NodeBB</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cve-2024-57041/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cve-2024-57041/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;stored-xss-exploit&#34;&gt;Stored XSS Exploit&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This discovery is particularly exciting as it marks a significant professional milestone: my first &lt;strong&gt;CVE&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;steps&#34;&gt;Steps&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Create an admin and another attacker user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The attacker navigates to their profile &amp;lsquo;about me&amp;rsquo; section and can post script tags into their &amp;lsquo;about me&amp;rsquo;.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/CVE-2024-57041/Image-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;XSS&#34; title=&#34;XSS&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The attacker can inject this payload: &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;script&amp;gt;alert(&amp;quot;NodeBB Hacked!&amp;quot;)&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/CVE-2024-57041/Image-2.png&#34; alt=&#34;XSS&#34; title=&#34;XSS&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/CVE-2024-57041/Image-3.png&#34; alt=&#34;XSS&#34; title=&#34;XSS&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once posted, the page will not yet reflect any of the stored script tags.&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/CVE-2024-57041/Image-4.png&#34; alt=&#34;XSS&#34; title=&#34;XSS&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an administrator, log into the application and visit the attacker users home page.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Junior Mobile Tester by TCM Security</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pjmt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pjmt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Certified Bug Bounty Hunter by Hack The Box&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.credential.net/11b2cfca-2bf6-4b95-b814-ecb702bbdc5c&#34;&gt;I am a certified PJMT!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;review-tcm-security-practical-mobile-penetration-tester-pmpt-certification&#34;&gt;Review: TCM Security Practical Mobile Penetration Tester (PMPT) Certification&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;PMPT certification&lt;/strong&gt; is a great option for those new to mobile penetration testing. I highly recommend both the training and the exam. However, for individuals with prior experience in mobile testing, this certification may not provide much of a challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-training&#34;&gt;The Training&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The training for this certification aligns perfectly with the exam material. There are no unexpected surprises, which makes it an excellent resource for beginners. I particularly enjoyed the training, as it introduced me to the fundamentals of hacking mobile applications in a clear and accessible way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box Certified Bug Bounty Hunter (HTB CBBH)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cbbh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cbbh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Certified Bug Bounty Hunter by Hack The Box&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.credly.com/badges/904e5947-ab72-4d9b-bb0f-0ca6ec1df3f7/public_url&#34;&gt;​I am a HTB CBBH!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;review-hack-the-box-certified-bug-bounty-hunter-cbbh-certification&#34;&gt;Review: Hack The Box Certified Bug Bounty Hunter (CBBH) Certification&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;CBBH certification&lt;/strong&gt; is a challenging yet rewarding experience. It offers significant value for those looking to enhance their skills in application security. I would highly recommend both the training and the exam for those serious about advancing in this area.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-training&#34;&gt;The Training&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The training for the CBBH certification was exceptional in many aspects. The content provided a deep understanding of application security and gave me a significant advantage in identifying vulnerabilities. However, not all modules were equally relevant—some felt confusing or disconnected from the core objectives of the exam. Thankfully, these instances were rare, and the overall quality of the training was excellent.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eWPT by INE/eLearnSecurity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ewpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ewpt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;eWPT by eLearnSecurity&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​&lt;a href=&#34;https://verified.elearnsecurity.com/certificates/db254803-1426-4b84-926f-72cb19b2422a&#34;&gt;​I am eWPT certified!&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;​&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;review-elearnsecurity-web-application-penetration-tester-ewpt-certification&#34;&gt;Review: eLearnSecurity Web Application Penetration Tester (eWPT) Certification&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the past few months, I’ve been working to deepen my understanding of web security while completing my master’s in cybersecurity. I wanted a certification that would help me strengthen my skills without adding too much to my already demanding workload. The &lt;strong&gt;eWPT&lt;/strong&gt; seemed like a good fit for that purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-training&#34;&gt;The Training&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The training for the eWPT aligned well with the exam material. While I found the training content to be fairly basic, I appreciated its focus on reinforcing foundational concepts. Building strong fundamentals is a priority for me as I prepare to tackle more advanced certifications in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eJPT by INE/eLearnSecurity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ejpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ejpt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;eJPT by eLearnSecurity&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​&lt;a href=&#34;https://verified.elearnsecurity.com/certificates/c04ac59f-d6eb-4e57-ae91-149f23ee8b28&#34;&gt;​I am eJPT certified!&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;​&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;review-elearnsecurity-junior-penetration-tester-ejpt-certification&#34;&gt;Review: eLearnSecurity Junior Penetration Tester (eJPT) Certification&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;eJPT certification&lt;/strong&gt; was my first-ever attempt at a cybersecurity certification. After completing a few more certifications and reflecting on the experiences of others, I can confidently say that the eJPT remains one of my favorite certifications to date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-training&#34;&gt;The Training&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;INE (formerly eLearnSecurity) provides the training material for the eJPT. While the training comes at a cost, it is thorough and more than sufficient to prepare for the exam. The course covers a wide range of fundamental topics, making it highly accessible for beginners. However, I strongly recommend taking detailed notes throughout the training, as the material does not emphasize note-taking methods—a skill that can significantly aid both your study process and exam performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
