<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>INE on Tony&#39;s Cybersecurity Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/ine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in INE on Tony&#39;s Cybersecurity Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Anthony Morell</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/ine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>eWPT by INE/eLearnSecurity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ewpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ewpt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;eWPT by eLearnSecurity&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​&lt;a href=&#34;https://verified.elearnsecurity.com/certificates/db254803-1426-4b84-926f-72cb19b2422a&#34;&gt;​I am eWPT certified!&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;​&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;review-elearnsecurity-web-application-penetration-tester-ewpt-certification&#34;&gt;Review: eLearnSecurity Web Application Penetration Tester (eWPT) Certification&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the past few months, I’ve been working to deepen my understanding of web security while completing my master’s in cybersecurity. I wanted a certification that would help me strengthen my skills without adding too much to my already demanding workload. The &lt;strong&gt;eWPT&lt;/strong&gt; seemed like a good fit for that purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-training&#34;&gt;The Training&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The training for the eWPT aligned well with the exam material. While I found the training content to be fairly basic, I appreciated its focus on reinforcing foundational concepts. Building strong fundamentals is a priority for me as I prepare to tackle more advanced certifications in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eJPT by INE/eLearnSecurity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ejpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ejpt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;eJPT by eLearnSecurity&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;​&lt;a href=&#34;https://verified.elearnsecurity.com/certificates/c04ac59f-d6eb-4e57-ae91-149f23ee8b28&#34;&gt;​I am eJPT certified!&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;​&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;review-elearnsecurity-junior-penetration-tester-ejpt-certification&#34;&gt;Review: eLearnSecurity Junior Penetration Tester (eJPT) Certification&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;eJPT certification&lt;/strong&gt; was my first-ever attempt at a cybersecurity certification. After completing a few more certifications and reflecting on the experiences of others, I can confidently say that the eJPT remains one of my favorite certifications to date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-training&#34;&gt;The Training&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;INE (formerly eLearnSecurity) provides the training material for the eJPT. While the training comes at a cost, it is thorough and more than sufficient to prepare for the exam. The course covers a wide range of fundamental topics, making it highly accessible for beginners. However, I strongly recommend taking detailed notes throughout the training, as the material does not emphasize note-taking methods—a skill that can significantly aid both your study process and exam performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
